livetrafficnetwork.com 2019-05-14

# Privacy Policy - BisectHosting - Quality Minecraft Server Hosting

    Last Edited on 2018-05-24	
    		   
    This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.
    
    **What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**
    
    When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other details to help you with your experience such as cookies and usage data.
    
    **When do we collect information?**
    
    We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or enter information on our site.
    
    **How do we use your information?**
    
    We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
    
          • To personalize user's experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
          • To improve our website in order to better serve you.
          • To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
          • To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
          • To quickly process your transactions.
          • To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.
          • To provide you with updates, special offers and discounts for our goods and services as well as general company information regarding your account.
          • To prevent fraudulent purchases e.g. Comparing your address with your credit card provider.
    
    **How do we protect visitor information?**
    
    We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.
    Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.
    
    We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.
    
    For your convenience we may store your credit card information kept for more than 60 days in order to expedite future orders, and to automate the billing process.
    
    **How long is data kept for?**
    
    Any data collected from you by us is kept until it is requested to be deleted, or is no longer required to prevent fraud.
    
    **Do we use 'cookies'?**
    
    Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
    
    We use cookies to:
          • Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.
          • Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.
          • Keep track of advertisements.
          • Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf.
    
    You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
    
    If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It won't affect the users experience that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.
    
    However, you can still place orders .

    **Third Party Disclosure**
    
    We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. 
    
    However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
    
    If you use the payment service PayPal or paysafecard to pay, your information will be stored and kept with them as per their Privacy Policy.
    
    Credit card payments are processed using Stripe, of which your card details, name, email address and mailing address are stored, which are required to process your card payments.
    
    **Third party links**
    
    Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
    
    **Google**
    
    Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en 
    
    We have not enabled Google AdSense on our site but we may do so in the future.
    
    **Facebook**
    
    We use Facebook analytics to track any purchase made using marketing through their siet. You can learn move about this at the following links:
    
    <https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950>
    <https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217>
    
    **Twitter**
    
    We use twitter advertisements to market our services to you, you can opt out of this here: https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170405
    
    **California Online Privacy Protection Act**
    
    CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf
    
    According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:
    Users can visit our site anonymously
    Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.
    Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy', and can be easily be found on the page specified above.
    
    Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:
          • On our Privacy Policy Page
    Users are able to change their personal information:
          • By emailing us
          • By logging in to their account
          • By chatting with us or sending us a ticket
    
    **Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?**
    It's also important to note that we allow third party behavioral tracking
    
    **COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**
    
    When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.
    
    We do not specifically market to children under 18.
    
    We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a childs parent or guardian and you believe your children have provided us with personal data, please contact us via our ticket system. If we are aware of a childs data being stored on our systems without verification or parental consent, we will remove the information from our systems.
    
    **Fair Information Practices**
    
    The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.
    
    In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:
    We will notify the users via email
          • Within 1 business day
    We will notify the users via in site notification
          • Within 1 business day
    
    We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.
    
    **CAN SPAM Act**
    
    The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.
    
    We collect your email address in order to:
          • Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
          • Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders
          • We may also send you additional information related to your product and/or service.
          • Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred
    
    To be accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:
          • NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses
          • Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way
          • Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters
          • Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
          • Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly
          • Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email
    
    If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can
          • Email us at contact@bisecthosting.com and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

    **Contacting Us**
    
    If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
    
    www.bisecthosting.com
    P.O. Box 24523
    Cleveland
    44124
    venturenodellc@gmail.com
